Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
6047
Kheel Center
109 linear ft.
Records.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into five sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Boxes 44-45 and 102-109 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Form and Genre Terms:
Records.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6047: Archives Information File
6047: Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
6047: Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
6047: Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
6047: Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Boxes 44-45 and 102-109 have not been inventoried at this time.
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 67, Folder: 1 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Manpower Problems and Their Effect on War Production, 1945; Publication (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Author: George Romney
    Notes: March 9, 1945
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Box: 67, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Productivity and Employment Costs in the Trunkline Industry, 1969; Publication (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Author: U.S. Civil Aeronautics Board
    Notes: October 1969
- Box: 67, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Selected References on Productivity, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Author: U.S. Department of Labor
    Notes: October 31, 1952
  - Item 2: Major Sources of Productivity Information, 1949; Publication (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Notes: June 1949
  - Item 3: Instructional Material on Productivity and Automation, 1965; Publication (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Author: University of Wisconsin
  - Item 4: Selected Publications on Productivity, 1966; Publication (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Notes: March 1, 1966
  - Item 5: Selected Publications on Productivity, Technology and Economic Growth, 1969; Publication (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Notes: January 31, 1969
- Box: 67, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Productivity Trends in the Malt Liquors Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Box: 67, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Indexes of Output per Person Employed and Per Man-Hour in Canada Commercial Nonagricultural Industries, Publication (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Author: Dominion Bureau of Statistics
  - Item 2: Prices, Productivity, and Canada's Competitive Position, Publication (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Author: Canadian Trade Committee
- Box: 67, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Productivity Trends in the Canning and Preserving Industries, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 6)
    Notes: January 1952
- Box: 67, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Human Implications of Work Study, 1960; Publication (Box 67, Folder 7)
    Author: Stuart Dalziel, Lisl Klein
- Box: 67, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Indexes of Output per Man-Hour, 1965; Publication (Box 67, Folder 8)
    Notes: November 1965
- Box: 67, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Realities of Productivity Bargaining, Publication (Box 67, Folder 9)
    Author: Institute of Personnel Management
- Box: 67, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Analysis of Production for 1950 in the Men's Clothing Industry, 1951; Publication (Box 67, Folder 10)
    Author: Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America
    Notes: March 1951
  - Item 2: Man-Hours Expended Per Dozen Men's Dress Shirts, 1948; Publication (Box 67, Folder 10)
    Notes: July 1948
- Box: 67, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance, 1951; Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Notes: August 1951
  - Item 2: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Dozen Men's Work Clothing, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Notes: May 1952
  - Item 3: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Men's Dress Shoes, 1951; Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Capital Requirements and Operating Ratios: Men's Shirt Industry, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Notes: September 1952
  - Item 5: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Men's Bib Overalls and Men's Work Jackets, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Man-Hours Expended Per Dozen Men's Dress Shirts, 1950; Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Notes: March 1950
  - Item 7: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Men's Work Pants, 1951; Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Notes: December 1951
  - Item 8: Man-Hours Expended Per Dozen Men's Dress and Sport Shirts, 1951; Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Notes: July 1951
  - Item 9: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance, 1951; Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Box: 67, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Bituminous-Coal-Mining Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Box: 67, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Anthracite Mining Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Box: 67, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Coke Oven Industries, Publication (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Box: 67, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Realities of Productivity Bargaining, Publication (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Productivity Bargaining and the Engineering Industry, 1968; Publication (Box 67, Folder 15)
    Author: Engineering Employers' Federation
    Notes: March 1968
  - Item 3: Productivity Agreements: the Processes of Negotiating and Communicating, Publication (Box 67, Folder 15)
    Author: The Industrial Society
  - Item 4: Productivity Bargaining, Publication (Box 67, Folder 15)
    Author: Confederation of British Industry
  - Item 5: Towards a High Wage, High Productivity Economy, Publication (Box 67, Folder 15)
    Author: F. James Fielding
  - Item 6: Productivity Bargaining: The British and American Experience, Publication (Box 67, Folder 15)
    Author: National Commission on Productivity
- Box: 67, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of a Conference on Productivity, 1950; Publication (Box 67, Folder 16)
    Notes: December 6, 1950
- Box: 67, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Glass Containers Industry Productivity Trends, Publication (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Copper Ores Mining Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Fine Cotton Gray Goods, 1954; Publication (Box 67, Folder 17)
    Notes: February 1954
  - Item 4: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Coarse Cotton Gray Goods, 1953; Publication (Box 67, Folder 17)
    Notes: March 1953
- Box: 67, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The British Cotton Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 18)
    Author: Anglo-American Council on Productivity
- Box: 67, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Ice Cream Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 19)
- Box: 67, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Produktivitetsfremmende Lonsystemer, Publication (Box 67, Folder 20)
    Author: Dansk Arbejdsgiverforening
    Language: Danish.
- Box: 67, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Dome Reflectors, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 21)
    Notes: March 1952
  - Item 2: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Street Lighting Luminaires, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 21)
    Notes: November 1952
  - Item 3: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Dry Electrolytic Capacitors, 1953; Publication (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Fluorescent Lighting Fixtures, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: 3-Pole Circuit Breakers, Circuit Interrupters, and Safety Switches, 1954; Publication (Box 67, Folder 21)
    Notes: July 1954
  - Item 6: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Radio and Television Manufacturing, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 21)
    Notes: February 1952
- Box: 67, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Household Electrical Appliances, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 22)
    Notes: October 1952
- Box: 67, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The R.E.F.A. System, Publication (Box 67, Folder 23)
    Author: European Productivity Agency
- Box: 67, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Ton in the Manufacture of Fertilizer, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 24)
- Box: 67, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Productivity in the Beet Sugar Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Productivity in the Beet Sugar Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Productivity Trends: Condensed and Evaporated Milk Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 25)
- Box: 67, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Qualitat, Kosten, Gewinn, Publication (Box 67, Folder 26)
    Author: Rita Heuer
    Language: German.
  - Item 2: Formen und Methoden der Rationalisierung in Westdeutschland, Publication (Box 67, Folder 26)
    Author: Karl-Heinz Pavel
  - Item 3: Lohnpolitik ohne Dogma, Publication (Box 67, Folder 26)
    Author: Franz Spiegelhalter
- Box: 67, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Glass Containers Industry Productivity Trends, Publication (Box 67, Folder 27)
- Box: 67, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The British Productivity Council, 1954; Publication (Box 67, Folder 28)
    Author: Office of the Council
    Notes: September 1954
  - Item 2: Trade Unions and Productivity, Publication (Box 67, Folder 28)
    Author: Conservative Party
  - Item 3: Planning, 1947; Publication (Box 67, Folder 28)
    Author: Political and Economic Planning
    Notes: January 3, 1947
  - Item 4: Fuller Employment, Publication (Box 67, Folder 28)
    Author: David Mitchell
  - Item 5: Productivity Agreements, Publication (Box 67, Folder 28)
    Author: Bert Ramelson
  - Item 6: Harold Wilson's Productivity Conference, Publication (Box 67, Folder 28)
    Author: Peter Jenkins
- Box: 67, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Productivity in British Industry, 1963; Publication (Box 67, Folder 29)
    Author: K.G.B. Bakewell
- Box: 67, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Productivity in the Hosiery Industries, Publication (Box 67, Folder 30)
- Box: 67, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Production Index for the Houston Area, Publication (Box 67, Folder 31)
    Author: Antonio Furino
- Box: 67, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: The Human Factor in Economic Growth, 1962; Publication (Box 67, Folder 32)
    Author: V.K.R.V. Rao
    Notes: October 25, 1962
- Box: 67, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Labor Productivity and Leadership-Patterns in Industrial Small Group in Japan, 1960; Publication (Box 67, Folder 33)
    Author: Shigeru Masato, Shoichi Isotani
  - Item 2: The Productivity Movement in Japan, 1964; Publication (Box 67, Folder 33)
    Author: Japan Productivity Center
- Box: 67, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Programa Interamericano de Productividad, 1960; Publication (Box 67, Folder 34)
    Author: Union Panamericana
    Notes: April 18-22, 1960
- Box: 67, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance, 1951; Publication (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Productivity Trends: Flour and Other Grain-Mill Products Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 35)
- Box: 67, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Types of Leather, 1948; Publication (Box 67, Folder 36)
    Notes: April 1948
- Box: 67, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Metal Forming Machinery, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Types of Machine Tools, 1951; Publication (Box 67, Folder 37)
    Notes: January 1951
  - Item 3: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Types of Machine Tools, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 37)
    Notes: June 1952
- Box: 67, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Types of Machine Tools, 1948; Publication (Box 67, Folder 38)
    Notes: November 1948
- Box: 67, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Types of General Industrial Equipment, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Types of General Industrial Equipment, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Types of Construction and Mining Machinery, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Types of Construction Machinery, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Item 5: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Types of Mining Machinery, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
- Box: 67, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Analiz Rezervov Rosta Proizvoditel'Nosti Truda, 1967; Publication (Box 67, Folder 40)
    Author: Viktor Pavlovich Radukin
    Language: Russian.
- Box: 67, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Cold Formed Machine Bolts and Hexagon Nuts, 1953; Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    Notes: October 1953
- Box: 67, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Poised for Defense, 1951; Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
    Author: Kansas Employment Security Division
    Notes: January-February 1951
- Box: 67, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Productivity Trends: Flour and Other Grain-Mill Products Industry, Publication (Box 67, Folder 43)
- Box: 67, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Output Per Man-Hour in Selected New England Industries, 1953; Publication (Box 67, Folder 44)
    Author: William H. Miernyk
    Notes: June 1953
- Box: 67, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Productivity Trends: Primary Smelting and Refining of Copper, Lead, and Zinc, Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - Item 2: Lead and Zinc Ores Mining Industries, Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
- Box: 68, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Office Output Can Be Planned, Measured, and Controlled, Publication (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Author: Paul B. Mulligan
- Box: 68, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance, 1954; Publication (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Notes: December 1954
- Box: 68, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Pulp and Paper Mills, 1951; Publication (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Box: 68, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Comparative Measurement of Productivity in the European Paper-Making Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Author: Organisation for Economic Co-Operation and Development
- Box: 68, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Indexes of Output Per Man-Hour: Petroleum Refining Industry, 1962; Publication (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Notes: January 1962
- Box: 68, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Review of Productivity in the Pharmaceutical Industry, Publication (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Author: British Productivity Council
- Box: 68, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Television and Radio Sets, 1951; Publication (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Box: 68, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Productivity Trends: Railroad Transportation Industry, Publication (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Selected Types of Railroad Freight Cars, 1950; Publication (Box 68, Folder 8)
    Notes: November 1950
- Box: 68, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Productivity Trends: Rayon and Other Synthetic Fibers Industry, Publication (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Box: 68, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Productivity Research Through Industrial Systems Simulation, 1963; Publication (Box 68, Folder 10)
    Author: Kenneth J. Schloger
    Notes: October 31, 1963
- Box: 68, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Productivity in Distribution, 1959; Publication (Box 68, Folder 11)
    Author: Organisation for European Economic Co-Operation
    Notes: January 20-23, 1959
- Box: 68, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Synthetic Rubber and Components, Publication (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Box: 68, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Productivity - Russia, 1949; Publication (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Author: Evstafev
  - Item 2: Soviet Attitudes and Policies Toward Increasing Output of Workers, 1957; Publication (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Notes: August 1957
  - Item 3: Productivity - Russia, 1968; Publication (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Author: Nikoliai Fedorovech Labedinskii
  - Item 4: Kachestuo Produktsii I Stimuly, 1967; Publication (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Author: Zakharn Semenovich Bogatyrenko
  - Item 5: Fiziologicheskoe Obosnovanie Metodov Povysheniia Proizveitel Nosti Truda, 1967; Publication (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Author: Sergei Aleksandrovich Kosilov
  - Item 6: Mis on Tootmise Rentaablus?, 1966; Publication (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Author: Sotsialistliku Majandamise Kool
  - Item 7: Trud v Nouoi Piatiletke, 1967; Publication (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Author: V.A. Rzhesheiishu
- Box: 68, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Productivity of Scientists, Publication (Box 68, Folder 14)
    Author: U.S. Department of Commerce
  - Item 2: Organizational Setting and Scientific Accomplishment, 1966; Publication (Box 68, Folder 14)
    Author: Gerald Gordon
- Box: 68, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Productivity in the Footwear Industry, Publication (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Selected Footwear, 1948; Publication (Box 68, Folder 15)
    Notes: March 1948
  - Item 3: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance: Women's Dress Shoes, 1951; Publication (Box 68, Folder 15)
    Notes: November 1951
  - Item 4: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Pair: Footwear, 1952; Publication (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Indexes of Output Per Man-Hour, 1965; Publication (Box 68, Folder 15)
    Notes: July 1965
  - Item 6: Productivity Issues in the Domestic Shoe Industry, Publication (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Box: 68, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Unit: Soap and Glycerin Manufacture, 1948; Publication (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Box: 68, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: International Comparisons of Labour Productivity in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 68, Folder 17)
    Author: United Nations
  - Item 2: Indexes of Output Per Man-Hour, 1964; Publication (Box 68, Folder 17)
    Notes: November 1964
- Box: 68, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Productivity in the Clay Construction Products Industry, Publication (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Productivity in the Glass Products Group, Publication (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Box: 68, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Productivity Trends in the Clay Construction Products Industries, 1951; Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Box: 68, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Instructor's Manual for Productivity, Publication (Box 68, Folder 20)
    Author: National Association of Manufacturers
- Box: 68, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Ton: Cane Sugar Refining, 1951; Publication (Box 68, Folder 21)
    Notes: June 1951
  - Item 2: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance, 1953; Publication (Box 68, Folder 21)
    Notes: February 1953
  - Item 3: Trends in Man-Hours Expended Per Ton, 1952; Publication (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Productivity in the Cane-Sugar Refining Industry, Publication (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Productivity in the Beet Sugar Industry, Publication (Box 68, Folder 21)
- Box: 68, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Productivity and Unit Labor Cost in the Telephone and Telegraph Industries, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
- Box: 68, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Productivity in the rayon and Allied Products Industry, Publication (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Indexes of Output Per Man-Hour, 1965; Publication (Box 68, Folder 23)
    Notes: October 1965
- Box: 68, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Indexes of Output Man-Hour in the Tires and Inner Tubes Industry, 1962; Publication (Box 68, Folder 24)
    Notes: October 1962
- Box: 68, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Productivity in the Tobacco Products Industries, Publication (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Productivity in the Tobacco Products Group, Publication (Box 68, Folder 25)
- Box: 68, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Indexes of Output Per Man-Hour for Selected Industries, 1960; Publication (Box 68, Folder 26)
    Notes: July 1960
  - Item 2: Indexes of Output Per Man-Hour, 1964; Publication (Box 68, Folder 26)
    Notes: September 1964
  - Item 3: Indexes of Output Per Man-Hour for selected Industries, Publication (Box 68, Folder 26)
    Notes: December 1961
- Box: 68, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Productivity and Bargaining, Publication (Box 68, Folder 27)
    Author: Harry F. Stark
- Box: 68, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Welding, 1951; Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
    Notes: August 29, 1951
- Box: 68, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Further Education for Technicians, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
    Author: City and Guilds of London Institute
- Box: 68, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: A Manual for the Preparation of Proposals, 1966; Publication (Box 68, Folder 30)
    Author: U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
    Notes: February 1966
  - Item 2: Professional Education in the Public Interest, 1966; Publication (Box 68, Folder 30)
    Notes: December 29, 1966
- Box: 68, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Careers in Technical Occupations, Publication (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Characteristics and Motivations of Scientific and Professional People, 1963; Publication (Box 68, Folder 31)
    Author: Dow Chemical Company
    Notes: June 11, 1963
  - Item 3: Employment Opportunities and Training Needs for Technicians in the State of Missouri with Projections Through 1970, Publication (Box 68, Folder 31)
    Author: Robert L. Prater